 _    _          _                           _                       
| |__| |_  _ ___| |__  ___ _ _ _ _ _  _   __| |_ _ ___ __ _ _ __  ___
| '_ \ | || / -_) '_ \/ -_) '_| '_| || | / _` | '_/ -_) _` | '  \(_-<
|_.__/_|\_,_\___|_.__/\___|_| |_|  \_, | \__,_|_| \___\__,_|_|_|_/__/
                                   |__/                              

= BLUEBERRY DREAMS =

* Version 1.0
* Updated 23 July 2007
* by DANNY, http://the-madness.net/blueberry-dreams/
                         
== General Information ==

Blueberry Dreams is a two-column theme for the Sandbox that is very light and very blue, and is also an entrant in the Sandbox Designs Competition (http://sndbx.org).  Blueberry Dreams is standards-compliant and has cross-browser compatibility. Being light on graphics, the style loads quickly for those using slow connections, yet is still beautiful to those on faster connections.

This style utilizes many beautiful shades of blue and has a cozy, journal-esque feeling associated with it.
Requirements

In order to install BD, the following are required:

    * Wordpress 2.x (as well as the WordPress requirements)
    * Sandbox 0.9.x
    
== Changelog ==

v. 1.1 - Made #menu look more like an important menu, fixed definition lists, and stopped the #nav div from riding up on the menu.

== File Tree ==

	sandbox-blueberry-dreams.zip [CONTAINS:]
		/blueberry-dreams/ [FOLDER]
			license.txt
			readme.txt
			style.css
			screenshot.png
			/images/ [SUBFOLDER]
				comment.gif
				folder.gif
				gradient.png
				header.png
				user.gif


== USING THIS DESIGN ==

** Please see howtoinstall.txt for information on installing this design.


== Quite Classy ==

BD is very classy. Here’s the lowdown:

    * the news class will generate text with a blue background and blue top- and bottom-borders. This is div-only (using it with a span will look ugly)
    * the important class will give your text an important-looking light blue background.
    * the caps class will capitalize your text.
    * by using <span class="amp"> & </span> instead of plain, old &, your ampersands will come out very sexy & beautiful.
    
== Thanks to... ==

    * Scott (http://sndbx.org) for building such an amazing theme and for organizing the contest (without which I would have had a somewhat boring summer!).
    * Mark James (http://famfamfam) for the mini silk icons (see license below).

== License ==

Blueberry Dreams © 2007 is licensed under the GNU General Public License:

        This program is free software; you can redistribute it and/or
        modify it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as
        published by the Free Software Foundation; either version 2 of
        the License, or (at your option) any later version.
    
        This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
        but without any warranty; without even the implied warranty of 
        merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose. See the 
        GNU General Public License for more details.
    
        You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public 
        License along with this program; if not, write to the Free
        Software Foundation, Inc, 51 Franklin Street, Fifth Floor,
        Boston, MA 02110-1301, USA.

== BTW ==

Linkbacks are always appreciated. :) http://the-madness.net
